websiteoptimization.com 2019-06-01

# Privacy Policy - Web Site Optimization, LLC

### Web Site Optimization, LLC

We take the privacy of your personal information seriously. We do not share your information with people outside of Web Site Optimization, LLC, without your express written consent. In the event that our business is acquired, our client list and newsletter list would also be a part of that transaction. Other than an acquisition or promotional purposes (testimonials) we do not share your personal information with any third party. Specifically:

What personal information is collected?
    We collect contact information from users, namely Name, Email address, Phone number, and the goals they want to achieve for their website.
How is this information used by WSO?
    WSO uses this contact information to contact interested visitors about the services they are interested in. We also collect and send out an e-mail newsletter to subscribers to our [Optimization Week](http://www.optimizationweek.com/) newsletter.
How does WSO transfer data to third-party companies?
    We do not share your personal information with third parties without your express written consent. Only in the event of an acquisition of our company will we share your personal information (client list, newsletter email list and interested users).
How do I modify or delete my personal information or opt-out?
    You can contact WSO through our Contact Form to request that we delete your personal information from our records. You can also unsubscribe to our newsletter by clicking on the unsubscribe link at the bottom of your most recent newsletter, or sending an unsubscribe request to the above contact form (please include the email address that you want to unsubscribe).

### Contact

Andy King - President  
Web Site Optimization, LLC  
Phone: 734.476.6611  
Contact Form
